Lysa Unku-Jones

Website: wildelyssa.github.io GitHub: https://github.com/Wildelyssa LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/lysa-unku-jones 07971 515195 lysa.jones@googlemail.com 111A Moray Road, London N4 3LB

Profile

I am a Junior Front-End Developer with a passion for coding. I have an active mind, and am committed to my professional development. My creativity is balanced with strong analytical skills, giving me a flair for functional layouts and design. I love to work collaboratively, sharing ideas and knowledge.

I am currently finishing a coding bootcamp with Zero to Mastery Academy, and have taken several extra courses alongside this, including topics such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Responsive Design. I have completed several small projects which are available on my GitHub.

Technical Skills

HTML and CSS

I write quality and concise HTML and CSS. I am forward thinking and aware of the big picture such as responsive design, scaleability, analytics, and anticipating potential issues.

JavaScript

Good foundational knowledge of JavaScript (ES6–10). I have a feel and understanding for the language, and a passion to learn more and become an expert.

HTML Emails

I have experience of designing and developing engaging and responsive HTML/CSS emails which are compatible with most popular email clients and campaign platforms — Outlook, Apple Mail, GMail, Hotmail, MailChimp, Campaign Monitor, Sendy, and so forth.

Personal Skills

Learning and Development

Keen and quick learner dedicated to continual self-improvement

I am a driven and enthusiastic student, who quickly picks up new processes. I challenge myself to keep up to date with the current standards and best practices, and continually learn and improve as a developer and a person.

Organisational

Strong organisation skills, accuracy, and attention to detail

I have an inquiring mind and an analytical and ordered nature. I love problem solving. Finding the most efficient route through a task gives me a sense of accomplishment. I live by daily and weekly planners, and love to be organised.

Communication and Team Working

Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills at all levels

Previously, I have worked in many customer-focused roles in many diverse working environments. I enjoy working in a collaborative team environment. I have excellent communication skills, and am a flexible and adaptable team player.

Creativity

Creative thinking and vision with the ability to see the big picture as well as the details

My natural creativity gives me a wider perspective and helps me find innovative ways of solving problems. I have an eye for design and style, as well as the functionality of a product.

Work Experience

Company	Description		
Holistic Therapist and Workshop Host Self-Employed London 2014-Present	Building and developing strong working relationships with clients and colleagues. Keeping accurate and up-to-date business and client records in compliance with Data Protection and GDPR. Writing copy for blog posts and promotional materials. Maintaining and updating website (HTML, CSS, Wordpress). Running and designing email marketing campaigns, including designing HTML emails. Social Media marketing through Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn. Collaborating with colleagues and studios to provide events, talks, and workshops. Giving high quality holistic treatments appropriate to the unique needs of each individual.		
Senior Stylist Lucinda Ellery Hair Consultants Ltd, London 2010–2014	Provide high quality hair replacement systems, extensions and solutions to hair loss. Working sensitively and professionally with a diverse clientele. All aspects of hair styling including styling lessons and aftercare advice. Finding creative solutions and managing change in a fast-paced environment. Working as part of a team to achieve high quality results for clients. Updating and maintaining electronic records. Answering phone queries and dealing with bookings.		
Junior Stylist The Salon, Birmingham 2008–2010	Working as part of a team providing all aspects of high quality hair styling. Managing own workload and supporting team-mates when appropriate. Reception duties including scheduling and managing bookings, taking payments, answering queries via email and phone. Providing reliable advice and suggestions for the needs of each client.		
Data Analyst/Health and Safety Officer Atkins Global, Birmingham 2005–2008	Analysing large datasets for Transport Planning and the Highways Agency. Working with Microsoft Excel, Access, Word, and Powerpoint. Accurately inputting data to databases. Finding and analysing patterns and anomalies in data and conducting research into causes. Producing graphs and reports in Excel and using in-house software. Reporting faults in data collection equipment. Completing Health and Safety audits. Providing Health and Safety training and inductions. Maintaining and updating accurate records.		

Formal Education

New College	Subject	Qualification	Grade
Telford, Shropshire	Physics	A-Level	В
	Mathematics	A-Level	С
	History	A-Level	А
	Archaeology	AS-Level	В
Wrockwardine Wood School Telford, Shropshire	History, Music, French	GCSE	A*
	English Literature, Chemistry	GCSE	А
	English Language, Biology, Physics, Maths, Graphics	GCSE	В